Laura: Hello, everybody.
Welcome to the class.
I’m Laura.
I’m your teacher.
OK, let’s go.
Look at me.
Dan: Hi, I’m Dan.
What’s your name?
Jasmine: Jasmine.
Dan: Sorry?
Jasmine: Jasmine!
Dan: Hey.
What’s your phone number?
Jasmine: It’s 936-555-0271.
Dan: 936-555-0271.
Jasmine: Yes. Text me.
Thanks.
Ed: Hi, Dan.
Dan: Hello.
This is Jasmine.
She’s in my salsa class.
Ed: Nice to meet you.
My name’s Ed.
Jasmine: Nice to meet you, too.
Dan: Bye, Jasmine.
Jasmine: Goodbye, Dan.
Bye, Ed.
Ed: Hi, Jasmine.
Jasmine: Ed!
Are you in the salsa class, too?
Ed: Yes, I am.
How are you?
Jasmine: I’m good, thank you.
And you?
Ed: Fine, thanks.
Laura: OK, everybody, with your partners.
Ed, you’re with Jasmine.
Ed: Great! You’re my partner!
Jasmine: Yes!
See you later, Dan.